{
  "id": "kanji",
  "title": "Kanji 漢字",
  "description": "Study set that includes cards to / from kanji characters, their on'yomi and kun'yomi readings, and meanings. Mnemonics for some of them are also  included as hints.",
  "topic": "japanese",
  "keys": {
    "K": "Kanji",
    "OY": "On'Yomi" ,
    "KY": "Kun'Yomi",
    "M": "Meaning",
    "MM": "Mnemonic",
    "T_HARD": "Hard",
    "T_LEARNED": "Learned",
    "T_NEW": "New"
  },
  "tags": [
    "T_HARD",
    "T_LEARNED",
    "T_NEW"
  ],
  "flashcards": {
    "RI1l+KhkjzALidLZpsxIc8QU4T4HCQ==": { "id": "RI1l+KhkjzALidLZpsxIc8QU4T4HCQ==", "front": "K", "back": "OY", "hint": "MM" },
    "FUZn2mO9nXuBlnonaW12m6ey3oWdpQ==": { "id": "FUZn2mO9nXuBlnonaW12m6ey3oWdpQ==", "front": "K", "back": "KY", "hint": "MM" },
    "9VrXesm1JWVJRQwc8v+hlSKzdhc2YQ==": { "id": "9VrXesm1JWVJRQwc8v+hlSKzdhc2YQ==", "front": "K", "back": "M", "hint": "MM" },
    "x3z+FOfkhzNPcf0xXEJRE6H52R1SZA==": { "id": "x3z+FOfkhzNPcf0xXEJRE6H52R1SZA==", "front": "OY", "back": "K", "hint": "MM" },
    "h9got83aJoNu8lP1LxCBxllRj/GA6Q==": { "id": "h9got83aJoNu8lP1LxCBxllRj/GA6Q==", "front": "OY", "back": "M", "hint": "MM" },
    "tx/kwtNVqHCZ2Pcthk4GP4XJE1i3rg==": { "id": "tx/kwtNVqHCZ2Pcthk4GP4XJE1i3rg==", "front": "KY", "back": "K", "hint": "MM" },
    "4H3YRWuQZAUx3OHg2H+TZD4xjcng+A==": { "id": "4H3YRWuQZAUx3OHg2H+TZD4xjcng+A==", "front": "KY", "back": "M", "hint": "MM" },
    "AhWk48S4jgEWVTgK9NjVryhIFzTvuQ==": { "id": "AhWk48S4jgEWVTgK9NjVryhIFzTvuQ==", "front": "M", "back": "K", "hint": "MM" },
    "V84fd78G/roC1ZaGu0MfAAiWNr9siQ==": { "id": "V84fd78G/roC1ZaGu0MfAAiWNr9siQ==", "front": "M", "back": "OY", "hint": "MM" },
    "ZeAa+o5CZI9/6TP50Rk0Xgj0A7l2jA==": { "id": "ZeAa+o5CZI9/6TP50Rk0Xgj0A7l2jA==", "front": "M", "back": "KY", "hint": "MM" }
  },
  "data": [
    { "id": "D65sVM32EZZP5PjMQ22v69tWM6jbtg==", "K": "一", "M": "One", "OY": "! いち, いつ", "KY": "ひと", "MM": "" },
    { "id": "iHIMwgCDEtQY0olq5P5eSsSjZvEHxA==", "K": "去", "M": "Past", "OY": "! きょ, こ", "KY": "さ", "MM": "Past is when you were a kid (子), when you were living in Kyoto (きょ)" },
    { "id": "rxtKUWidFVH9irX/9YjZVUTtvVFYdA==", "K": "号", "M": "Number", "OY": "! ごう", "KY": "-", "MM": "This kanji consists of two numbers, 0 and 5 on top of each other. That's why reading starts with (ご): ごう" },
    { "id": "rBgfrYlcrx2ME2PAlM/lO/ReNhnrgA==", "K": "央", "M": "Center", "OY": "! おう", "KY": "-", "MM": "Looks like middle (中) kanji. In the center, there is always the king (おう), thus the reading." },
    { "id": "p83JR6NDiK85n5RmICZy1egSh7oiEA==", "K": "打", "M": "Hit", "OY": "! だ", "KY": "う, ぶ", "MM": "Left part is fingers radical, right part looks like child radical. Think of this as HITting a child, a typical case of dayak (だ)" },
    { "id": "Imfcp7dT5Yg71uvb+SHdhMZQgurN0Q==", "K": "氷", "M": "Ice", "OY": "ひょう", "KY": "! こおり", "MM": "In the core (こお) of ice, there is a ring (り). Marriage proposals are getting creative." },
    { "id": "QgqXjj5FZZ4CQh2tay5hmt+bMcELFQ==", "K": "申", "M": "Say Humbly", "OY": "しん", "KY": "! もう",  "MM": "This consists of a cross and a mouth. Something like controlling your mouth to speak humbly instead of sounding like an asshole. As for the reading, remember from the involvement of the mouth (もう) radical. This kanji is also used for saying 'hello' on the phone: '申し申し' so remember もう from there." },
    { "id": "f2yzBOhp50oyMkWNAPdmJUmGQj6T3w==", "K": "先", "M": "Previous, Ahead, Past, Former", "OY": "! せん", "KY": "さき, まず", "MM": "There's a 'pi' in this kanji, (pi)revious. Remember from your mom telling you a story about the past: (sen - せん)eler evvel (sen - せん) doğmadan önce, ..." },
    { "id": "", "K": "", "OY": "", "KY": "", "M": "", "MM": "" }
  ]
}
